I'm going to surprise Oharu and Julia.
I'll do it first.
Wait a minute, Julia.
I'll do it.
Don't say it.
I'll do it when I think it's over.
I'll do it.
Why?
We have only 10 minutes.
We have to upload it in 10 minutes.
I think we'll be notified when we
upload it.
We have only 10 minutes.
Who are you going to call?
I'm going to call someone.
I'm going to call Julia.
I'm going to call her.
I can do it.
Are you OK?
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to my channel.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thank you for watching.
I will do my best to read this.
I'm sorry.
I thought I was going to read this.
I don't read people's letters.
That's true.
I'm going to read it all.
Aki-chan asked us if we should wear
more eye makeup.
I've been wearing makeup lately.
Should we call someone?
Someone?
Thank you!
How are you feeling?
Are you nervous?
Not really.
I can't see the nervousness.
I was more nervous yesterday.
Really?
Yesterday...
Yesterday,
we were on
STAFF LAB radio.
We were on the radio together.
I'm so nervous.
It's been a while since you were on the
radio.
When we were about to go home,
I put on my shoes.
When I put on both shoes,
I realized that I put them on the
opposite side.
I had to put them on again.
I was walking and I was like,
what's wrong?
I was going home after that.
Hiyori was biting me.
I don't know what she was saying.
I was so surprised.
She was biting me.
It was just a conversation.
I got a message.
I'm sorry
I'm back.
I was surprised to see you here.
I couldn't hear your voice.
I was wondering where you were calling
me.
You were talking loudly.
Happy New Year.
I was waiting for you.
I'm glad you called me.
Today is your birthday.
How do you feel?
I'm glad to hear that.
You're 16 years old.
You're young.
How many years ago?
4 years ago?
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Oharu.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You're so weak.
I thought you were strong.
Let's go to Oharu.
Only twice.
I'm glad to hear that.
I got a lot of messages from you.
I thought you didn't notice.
I did.
I thought something was going on.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you.
Can I go now?
I'll open it later.
I'll do the surprise later.
.
This program is brought to you by six
people who are active to promote
something exciting.
We also do three things while talking
about our future with six female
students!
I'll prove it!
Happy New Day!
I'm nervous.
I think my hair is about the same
length as the second group.
P.O's hair is probably the same length
as the second group.
I think Aki-chan's hair is about the
same length as the second group.
I'm going to kill you.
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to my channel.
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to my channel!
The rehearsal is over!
Thank you for the rehearsal!
Thank you for your support!
The rehearsal begins!
The rehearsal is over!
I'm nervous but I'll do my best!
The point of this costume is...
All of my wrists are made of clothes.
So, that's the point!
I don't have much time left but...
I'll eat a bento.
I want to eat a bento.
Today is the day of the live.
Let's eat!
Kiki is good at sweet talk.
Please give me a reward.
I'm going to act.
Relax.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Looking forward to the next victory
game!
Chuити- calculation one muchimp
There is a feel like your ears will get
torn
To advertise something exciting
You're enthusiasm goes up
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thanks for watching!
Today is the first live performance of
Toki-chan, so let's enjoy it together
until the end!
It was my first time to hold a birthday
party like this, and I've never had so
many people celebrate me like this
before.
I'm happy that there are many messages
of support and birthday congratulations.
Thank you!
I'm happy! I'm 16 years old, but I'm 2
years old and I'm an adult.
So I want to be 16 years old, where I
can improve my communication skills,
talking skills, singing and dancing.
I want to challenge myself to do more
things at 16 years old. I want to be 16
years old and say, I've done it!
By the way, I'm 15 years old and I've
done it!
I'm 16 years old and I'll keep doing a
lot of promotion activities! Please wait
for me!
I'm 16 years old!
Thank you for your hard work!
It's the birthday girl's birthday!
Aki-chan!
I couldn't see you!
Happy birthday!
You look great in that outfit!
I'm sorry!
You look so cute!
Look at me!
That way?
A little more!
A little more?
I'm going to sleep now.
How was your birthday?
It's amazing!
It was fun, but I don't know what to
do.
I'm so nervous.
I was wondering what to do.
But I was happy and fun.
I won't regret it, so I'll do my best
next time.
I'll do my best!
It smells good.
Congratulations on your 15th
anniversary!
Thank you!
You are definitely
That's not funny at all!
Thank you!!
Don't be afraid!
I'll do it later.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Ahaha!
Sorry, sorry.
Ready, set, go!
Ta-da!
Wow!
This is amazing!
Thank you!
It's ice cream!
Wow!
What's this?
This is a warm blanket.
This is my favorite item.
It's warm and has vibration.
So, I can put my feet in it.
And I can put my legs in it.
Wow!
I'll put both of them in it.
Thank you!
I'm sorry.
I'm a little bit shy.
I was told that I like this song.
When I was told that, I suddenly said,
Happy birthday to you.
Thank you!
What is that?
It's a toner!
It's an energy lotion!
Energy?
And...
Biology!
This is Radiant Touch Blur Primer.
It's a base, but...
I was thinking of buying it someday.
I'm glad I got it.
Thank you for watching!
I'll do my best to make it more
beautiful.
You're like a senior in her 20s.
I think I did it.
Please subscribe to my channel!
I want you to know that I want to be
your type of girl.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
My heart is beating because of you.
Let's have more fun tomorrow.
I'll always draw you.
I'll always be by your side.
I'm always thinking about you.
It's a very important time for me to be
able to perform live like this.
I believe that there will be more fun
days than now so that I will not let my
dreams end in my dreams.
I'm looking forward to seeing beautiful
scenery together.
Let's meet again! I'm looking forward
to it!
Let's dye the venue orange with the
same smile, a lot of smiles!
I can't express my feelings clearly
enough
This feeling is mysterious again
Ah, this is love
You're a youth heart shaker
This love is troublesome but it's the
best
I feel like I don't have to hate myself
Why is it that when I smile, the world
seems to shine?
I can turn my umbrella around and feel
better
Because I can't walk without it
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I wonder if I'll get wet again
somewhere and not feel cold
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I just want to share my feelings
A scenery I don't know yet in front of
my eyes
Hey, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colorful
On the canvas of my damaged heart
I'll draw a fragment of the future
It will guide me
Now is the night, the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of rain drops is ringing
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a flower, the sound of
rain drops is ringing
I wear a rainbow dress
Translated by Releska